thefactsaboutfitness.com 2013-12-30

# Privacy Policy

The following statement explains our policy regarding the personal information we collect about you, and is effective from 1 October 2011.

**1\. Statement of intent** You may be asked to submit personal information about yourself (such as your name and e-mail address) in order to receive or use services on our website. Such services include newsletters, surveys and membership to the site. Whenever you provide such personal information, we will treat that information in accordance with this policy. Our services are designed to give you the information that you want to receive. We will act in accordance with current legislation and aim to meet current Internet best practice.

**2\. Information on visitors** During the course of any visit to thefactsaboutfitness.com, the pages you see, along with something called a cookie, are downloaded to your computer (see point 3 for more on this). Most, if not all, websites do this, because cookies allow the website publisher to do useful things like find out whether the computer (and probably its user) has visited the site before. This is done on a repeat visit by checking to see, and finding, the cookie left there on the last visit.

Any information that is supplied by cookies can help us to provide you with a better service and helps us meet the needs and goals of our visitors.

Log files provide non-personal statistical information about visits to pages on the site, the duration of individual page view, paths taken by visitors through the site, data on visitors’ screen settings and other general information. The factsaboutfitness.com uses this type of information to help it improve the services to its users.

**3\. What is a cookie?** When you enter a site your computer will automatically be issued with a cookie. Cookies are text files that identify your computer to our server. Cookies in themselves do not identify the individual user, just the computer used. Many sites do this whenever a user visits their site in order to track traffic flows.

Cookies themselves only record those areas of the site that have been visited by the computer in question, and for how long. Users have the opportunity to set their computers to accept all cookies, to notify them when a cookie is issued, or not to receive cookies at any time. The last of these, of course, means that certain personalized services cannot then be provided to that user.

**4\. Use and storage of your personal information** When you supply any personal information to thefactsaboutfitness.com (e.g. to receive the newsletter) we will explain how we will use it and tell you if we want to pass the information on to anyone else. Any information you provide to thefactsaboutfitness.com will only be used by us. It will never be rented, traded or sold, unless we are obliged by law to disclose it.

We will hold your information on our systems for as long as you use the service you have requested, and remove it in the event that the purpose has been met, or you request that we remove it.

If you wish to update your personal information, please send your request to support@thefactsaboutfitness.com

You can also write to us at:

The Facts About Fitness Ltd.  
14 Hares Run  
Mawsley  
Northamptonshire  
United Kingdom  
NN14 1TG

**5\. Advertising** We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please go to <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/>.
